TARYN MOORE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

713-857-1967

x tarynmoore628@gmail.com

Salt Lake City, Utah

in @taryn-moore-a4466b7a

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPER CERTIFICATE

University of Utah End Date: Oct 1, 2022

ASSOCIATES DEGREE

Elementary Education
Salt Lake Community College
2014 – 2016

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Express.js

Node.js

MySQL

MongoDb

Git

SUMMARY

My professional career has been spent working in my local community. I have ranged from serving at local restaurants to managing.

I have furthered my Education at the University of Utah to learn how to be a full stack web developer. I am proficient in multiple languages that work with the front-end, back-end, and databases.

EXPERIENCE

SERVER

Tsunami | Feb 2019 - Oct 2022

A local restaurant that has everyones favorite, sushi! 3+ years of learning to think quickly on my feet, customer relations, and committed to all of the owners goals.

- Influenced owners to get a new system. Assisted in making it user friendly and linked to all aspects of the restaurant.
- Able to work in high pressure situations while focusing on the customer's experience.
- Trained new employees which entailed bar service, memorizing the menus, and best practices to keep the flow of the workspace.

EXECUTIVE MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT

Athena | Oct 2017 - Jan 2019

Reported to the owner of a local cafe. Worked very closely with the owner to launch the cafe, hire staff, and maintain high expectations of quality.

- Accomplished creating the credit-card, payroll, and scheduling system.
- Researched best equipment to use. This included reaching out to vendors, and suppliers.
- Assisted in day-to-day tasks including packages, phone calls, and meetings.

MANAGER

Beaumont Bakery & Cafe | Jan 2017 - Oct 2017

Managed employees working in the cafe while working as a team with co-managers. Contributed to the grand opening, and helped with the flow of the cafe.

- Oversaw the schedules, training, and hiring of employees.
- Created the steps of service, organization tools, and daily tasks.
- Provided new menu items, and maintained the standard set by the owners.